It is a first computer game,
actually a fan-made addon in which I partake
by providing my voice.
We do not fight for influence, it is about survival
and the shape of our kingdom as we know it.
King Rhobar II is a multidimensional character.
On the one hand, he united whole Myrthana under his dominion.
On the other hand, he has been
completely defeated in the clash with enemies
the Orcs.
He began to draw despotic and radical decisions out against the rising threat.
He is strong,
but the strength proves to be worthless, when he is balancing on the edge of a precipice.
They neither know about compromise, nor mercy. Hence we should act without remorse, albeit prudentially.
‘The History of Khorinis’
is a non-commercial work.
I’m impressed
by professionalism
and attention to details.
I strongly recommend,
Ryszard Mróz